Beneath the surface lies a burning secret.
Fire is a drama, romance film directed by Deepa Mehta.
In a barren, arranged marriage to an amateur swami who seeks enlightenment through celibacy, Radha's life takes an irresistible
turn when her beautiful young sister-in-law seeks to free herself from the confines of her own loveless marriage.
Sita, played by Nandita Das.
Radha, played by Shabana Azmi.
Jatin, played by Javed Jaffrey.
Ashok, played by Kulbhushan Kharbanda.
Biji, played by Kushal Rekhi.
Mundu, played by Ranjit Chowdhry.
Fire Down Below is a 1997 American action film directed by
Félix Enríquez Alcalá in his directorial debut.
The film stars Steven Seagal (who also co-produced the film) as Jack Taggert, an EPA agent who investigates a Kentucky mine and helps locals stand up for their rights, and also includes cameos by country music
performers Randy Travis, Mark Collie, Ed Bruce, Marty Stuart and Travis Tritt as well as country-rocker and the Band member Levon Helm, along with Kris Kristofferson appearing in a supporting role.
The film was released in the United States on September 5,
1997, to critical and commercial failure.
The film explores themes of coming out, infidelity, husband
wife relationship, arranged marriage, hinduism.
The tone is emotional.